seoengine.com 2016-05-02

# Privacy Policy — Market Brew

**Privacy Policy**

This [Market Brew](http://www.marketbrew.com/) privacy policy sets out how Marketbrew.com uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from November 12, 2014.

 **What we collect**

We may collect the following information:

  * name and job title
  * contact information including email address and phone number
  * demographic information such as city/state, postcode, preferences and interests
  * company name and website
  * company advertising spend on SEO and PPC and provider information
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

 **What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and [provide you with a better service](http://www.marketbrew.com/predictive-platform/), and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to [improve our products](http://www.marketbrew.com/search-engine-model/) and services.
  * We may use the information for conducting a product demo and sales related purposes.
  * We may periodically send promotional email or mail about new products, special offers, newsletters or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, or mail.
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
  * We may provide your information to our third party partners for marketing or promotional purposes.
  * We will never sell your information.

 **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs.

As you browse Marketbrew.com and other websites, online ad networks we work with may place anonymous cookies on your computer, and use similar technologies, in order to understand your interests based on your (anonymous) online activities, and thus to tailor more relevant ads to you. If you do not wish to receive such tailored advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ to opt out of most companies that engage in such advertising.  (This will not prevent you from seeing ads; the ads simply will not be delivered through these targeting methods.)

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

 **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * by unsubscribing to any newsletters or marketing emails that we send you. There will be a link on the email indicating how to unsubscribe.
  * if you do not want your personal information used for direct marketing purposes or any purpose, you may notify us any time by emailing privacy[at]marketbrew[dot]com.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us at privacy[at]marketbrew[dot]com.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
